{
  "Name": "Hiragana",
  "Description": "A set for learning the Japanese syllabary - Hiragana. On one side is a syllabe in the Hiragana, and on the other is its Romaji transcription. Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hiragana",
  "Cards": [
    {
      "Question": "あ",
      "Answer": "a"
    },
	{
      "Question": "い",
      "Answer": "i"
    },
	{
      "Question": "う",
      "Answer": "u"
    },
	{
      "Question": "え",
      "Answer": "e"
    },
	{
      "Question": "お",
      "Answer": "o"
    },
	{
      "Question": "か",
      "Answer": "ka"
    },
	{
      "Question": "き",
      "Answer": "ki"
    },
	{
      "Question": "く",
      "Answer": "ku"
    },
	{
      "Question": "け",
      "Answer": "ke"
    },
	{
      "Question": "こ",
      "Answer": "ko"
    },
	{
      "Question": "さ",
      "Answer": "sa"
    },
	{
      "Question": "し",
      "Answer": "shi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "す",
      "Answer": "su"
    },
	{
      "Question": "せ",
      "Answer": "se"
    },
	{
      "Question": "そ",
      "Answer": "so"
    },
	{
      "Question": "た",
      "Answer": "ta"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ち",
      "Answer": "chi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "つ",
      "Answer": "tsu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "て",
      "Answer": "te"
    },
	{
      "Question": "と",
      "Answer": "to"
    },
	{
      "Question": "な",
      "Answer": "na"
    },
	{
      "Question": "に",
      "Answer": "ni"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぬ",
      "Answer": "nu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ね",
      "Answer": "ne"
    },
	{
      "Question": "の",
      "Answer": "no"
    },
	{
      "Question": "は",
      "Answer": "ha"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ひ",
      "Answer": "hi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ふ",
      "Answer": "fu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "へ",
      "Answer": "he"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ほ",
      "Answer": "ho"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ま",
      "Answer": "ma"
    },
	{
      "Question": "み",
      "Answer": "mi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "む",
      "Answer": "mu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "め",
      "Answer": "me"
    },
	{
      "Question": "も",
      "Answer": "mo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "や",
      "Answer": "ya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゆ",
      "Answer": "yu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "よ",
      "Answer": "yo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ら",
      "Answer": "ra"
    },
	{
      "Question": "り",
      "Answer": "ri"
    },
	{
      "Question": "る",
      "Answer": "ru"
    },
	{
      "Question": "れ",
      "Answer": "re"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ろ",
      "Answer": "ro"
    },
	{
      "Question": "わ",
      "Answer": "wa"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゐ",
      "Answer": "i"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ゑ",
      "Answer": "e"
    },
	{
      "Question": "を",
      "Answer": "o"
    },
	{
      "Question": "きゃ",
      "Answer": "kya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "きゅ",
      "Answer": "kyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "きょ",
      "Answer": "kyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "しゃ",
      "Answer": "sha"
    },
	{
      "Question": "しゅ",
      "Answer": "shu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "しょ",
      "Answer": "sho"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ちゃ",
      "Answer": "cha"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ちゅ",
      "Answer": "chu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ちょ",
      "Answer": "cho"
    },
	{
      "Question": "にゃ",
      "Answer": "nya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "にゅ",
      "Answer": "nyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "にょ",
      "Answer": "nyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ひゃ",
      "Answer": "hya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ひゅ",
      "Answer": "hyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ひょ",
      "Answer": "hyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "みゃ",
      "Answer": "mya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "みゅ",
      "Answer": "myu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "みょ",
      "Answer": "myo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "りゃ",
      "Answer": "rya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "りゅ",
      "Answer": "ryu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "りょ",
      "Answer": "ryo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "が",
      "Answer": "ga"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぎ",
      "Answer": "gi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぐ",
      "Answer": "gu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "げ",
      "Answer": "ge"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ご",
      "Answer": "go"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ざ",
      "Answer": "za"
    },
	{
      "Question": "じ",
      "Answer": "ji"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ず",
      "Answer": "zu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぜ",
      "Answer": "ze"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぞ",
      "Answer": "zo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "だ",
      "Answer": "da"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぢ",
      "Answer": "ji"
    },
	{
      "Question": "づ",
      "Answer": "zu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "で",
      "Answer": "de"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ど",
      "Answer": "do"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ば",
      "Answer": "ba"
    },
	{
      "Question": "び",
      "Answer": "bi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぶ",
      "Answer": "bu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "べ",
      "Answer": "be"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぼ",
      "Answer": "bo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぱ",
      "Answer": "pa"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぴ",
      "Answer": "pi"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぷ",
      "Answer": "pu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぺ",
      "Answer": "pe"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぽ",
      "Answer": "po"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぎゃ",
      "Answer": "gya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぎゅ",
      "Answer": "gyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぎょ",
      "Answer": "gyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "じゃ",
      "Answer": "ja"
    },
	{
      "Question": "じゅ",
      "Answer": "ju"
    },
	{
      "Question": "じょ",
      "Answer": "jo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぢゃ",
      "Answer": "ja"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぢゅ",
      "Answer": "ju"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぢょ",
      "Answer": "jo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "びゃ",
      "Answer": "bya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "びゅ",
      "Answer": "byu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "びょ",
      "Answer": "byo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぴゃ",
      "Answer": "pya"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぴゅ",
      "Answer": "pyu"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ぴょ",
      "Answer": "pyo"
    },
	{
      "Question": "ん",
      "Answer": "n"
    }
  ]
}